// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from ".";

export const coheed: Topic = {
  topic: "Coheed and Cambria",
  level: "Beginner",
  totalQuestions: 150,
  totalScore: 750,
  totalTime: 3600,
  questions: [
    {
      question: "What was Coheed and Cambria's first single?",
      choices: [
        "Junesong Provision",
        "Time Consumer",
        "Devil In Jersey City",
        "Hearshot Kid Disaster",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Devil In Jersey City"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's first studio album?",
      choices: [
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV, Vol. 1",
        "The Color Before the Sun",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV, Vol. 2",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What year was The Second Stage Turbine Blade released?",
      choices: ["2003", "2001", "2004", "2002"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2002"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What year was In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3 released?",
      choices: ["2003", "2004", "2005", "2006"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2003"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What year was Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV, Vol. 1 released?",
      choices: ["2004", "2005", "2006", "2007"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2005"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What year was Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV, Vol. 2 released?",
      choices: ["2005", "2006", "2007", "2008"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2007"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What year was Year of the Black Rainbow released?",
      choices: ["2010", "2008", "2009", "2011"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2010"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What year was The Afterman: Ascension released?",
      choices: ["2012", "2011", "2010", "2013"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2012"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What year was The Afterman: Descension released?",
      choices: ["2012", "2010", "2013", "2014"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2013"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What year was The Color Before the Sun released?",
      choices: ["2011", "2012", "2015", "2016"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2015"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "In what year was Coheed and Cambria formed?",
      choices: ["1998", "2001", "2003", "2005"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["1998"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "Who are the founding members of Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez and Josh Eppard",
        "Claudio Sanchez and Travis Stever",
        "Travis Stever and Josh Eppard",
        "Claudio Sanchez, Travis Stever, and Michael Todd",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez and Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's debut album?",
      choices: [
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of the band joined after the release of their debut album?",
      choices: ["Travis Stever", "Josh Eppard", "Michael Todd", "Zach Cooper"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Josh Eppard"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What inspired Claudio Sanchez to create The Amory Wars, the conceptual universe in Coheed and Cambria's albums?",
      choices: ["A book series", "A dream", "A movie", "A graphic novel"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A graphic novel"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album marked a departure from The Amory Wars concept?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What song by Coheed and Cambria gained significant mainstream success and radio play?",
      choices: [
        "The Crowing",
        "Welcome Home",
        "A Favor House Atlantic",
        "Gravity's Union",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Welcome Home"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's official fan club?",
      choices: [
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "The Children of the Fence",
        "The Keywork Collective",
        "The Amory Guild",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Children of the Fence"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria temporarily left the band but later returned?",
      choices: ["Josh Eppard", "Travis Stever", "Michael Todd", "Chris Pennie"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Josh Eppard"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What significant event led to the formation of Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: [
        "A shared vision",
        "A chance meeting",
        "A high school friendship",
        "A mutual love for progressive rock",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A high school friendship"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is the primary lyricist and creative force behind The Amory Wars concept?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In what city did Claudio Sanchez and Travis Stever form the band Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: ["New York City", "Boston", "Los Angeles", "Seattle"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["New York City"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album serves as the prequel to The Amory Wars and provides insights into the origins of the storyline?",
      choices: [
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What inspired Claudio Sanchez to create the character 'Coheed Kilgannon'?",
      choices: [
        "A family member",
        "A friend",
        "A comic book character",
        "A historical figure",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A family member"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which album marked the return of Josh Eppard to Coheed and Cambria after a temporary departure?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Descension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's first studio album?",
      choices: [
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2012, which member of Coheed and Cambria was replaced by Zach Cooper as the bassist?",
      choices: ["Michael Todd", "Chris Pennie", "Travis Stever", "Josh Eppard"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Michael Todd"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What event served as the catalyst for Claudio Sanchez to start writing the story of The Amory Wars?",
      choices: [
        "A personal tragedy",
        "A dream",
        "A science fiction movie",
        "A road trip",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A personal tragedy"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which song by Coheed and Cambria is considered a tribute to Claudio Sanchez's dog, Apollo?",
      choices: [
        "Welcome Home",
        "The Suffering",
        "Feathers",
        "The Running Free",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Feathers"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What role did Nate Kelley play in the early years of Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: ["Lead vocalist", "Drummer", "Bassist", "Lead guitarist"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Drummer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the original name of Coheed and Cambria before they changed it to the current name?",
      choices: [
        "Shabütie",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "Weerd Science",
        "The Amory Wars",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Shabütie"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "During their early years, what genre of music did Coheed and Cambria primarily identify with?",
      choices: ["Punk rock", "Post-hardcore", "Progressive metal", "Emo"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Punk rock"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which venue played a crucial role in Coheed and Cambria's early success in the New York music scene?",
      choices: ["CBGB", "Whisky a Go Go", "The Roxy Theatre", "The Troubadour"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["CBGB"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In what year did Coheed and Cambria sign their first major record deal?",
      choices: ["1998", "2001", "2003", "2005"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2003"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which influential producer worked with Coheed and Cambria on their breakthrough album 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3'?",
      choices: [
        "Butch Vig",
        "David Bottrill",
        "Chris Bittner",
        "Michael Birnbaum",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Michael Birnbaum"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of the song 'The Camper Velourium III: Al the Killer' in Coheed and Cambria's discography?",
      choices: [
        "It's a tribute to a fan",
        "It's a concept for a movie",
        "It's part of The Amory Wars storyline",
        "It's a cover song",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["It's part of The Amory Wars storyline"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which album marked the departure of drummer Josh Eppard and the temporary inclusion of drummer Taylor Hawkins?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What notable event in 2004 boosted Coheed and Cambria's mainstream visibility?",
      choices: [
        "A Grammy Award nomination",
        "A performance on Saturday Night Live",
        "A collaboration with a popular artist",
        "A cover feature in Rolling Stone",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A Grammy Award nomination"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album served as a prequel to 'The Amory Wars' storyline and explored the character Sirius Amory?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the graphic novel series that Claudio Sanchez co-wrote, expanding on The Amory Wars narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman",
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Bag.On.Line Adventures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria took on the persona of 'Sirius Amory' during 'The Amory Wars' concept?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's first EP, released before their debut album?",
      choices: [
        "The Penelope EP",
        "The Delirium Trigger EP",
        "The Shabütie EP",
        "The Elf Tower New Mexico EP",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Penelope EP"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2007, Coheed and Cambria contributed a song to the soundtrack of which popular science fiction film?",
      choices: [
        "Star Wars: The Force Awakens",
        "Blade Runner 2049",
        "Transformers",
        "Ender's Game",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Transformers"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which album by Coheed and Cambria marked a return to The Amory Wars concept after a brief departure?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the documentary that provides insights into the making of Coheed and Cambria's album 'The Color Before the Sun'?",
      choices: [
        "Beyond the Fence",
        "The Afterman Chronicles",
        "Unheavenly Creatures Unleashed",
        "Making Colors",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Beyond the Fence"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which song by Coheed and Cambria was inspired by Claudio Sanchez's experience with sleep paralysis?",
      choices: ["Gravity's Union", "The Hard Sell", "The Crowing", "Ghost"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Gravity's Union"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's coffee table book released in 2021?",
      choices: [
        "The Amory Wars Chronicles",
        "The Unheavenly Coffee Table",
        "Vaxis Visualized",
        "Year of the Coffee Table",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis Visualized"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "During the recording of 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3,' which member of the band temporarily left, leading to Chris Pennie joining as the drummer?",
      choices: [
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Michael Todd",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Josh Eppard"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the comic book series co-written by Claudio Sanchez that delves into the backstory of 'The Amory Wars' characters?",
      choices: [
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
        "The Afterman",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Bag.On.Line Adventures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2022, Coheed and Cambria celebrated the anniversary of which album with a special re-release?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the title of Coheed and Cambria's first demo album released in 1999?",
      choices: [
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "Plan to Take Over the World",
        "The Penelope EP",
        "The Delirium Trigger EP",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Plan to Take Over the World"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which influential progressive rock band did Coheed and Cambria tour with, helping them gain early exposure?",
      choices: ["Rush", "Genesis", "Yes", "Pink Floyd"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Used"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2006, Coheed and Cambria released a limited-edition graphic novel accompanying which album?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which song by Coheed and Cambria served as the theme for the animated series 'American Dad!'?",
      choices: [
        "A Favor House Atlantic",
        "The Suffering",
        "Welcome Home",
        "Feathers",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Welcome Home"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the significance of the song 'The Willing Well IV: The Final Cut' in Coheed and Cambria's discography?",
      choices: [
        "It's a cover song",
        "It's a live recording",
        "It's the last track on their debut album",
        "It's part of The Amory Wars storyline",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["It's part of The Amory Wars storyline"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2015, Coheed and Cambria launched a record label. What is the name of this label?",
      choices: [
        "Evil Ink Records",
        "Keywork Records",
        "Heed Your Call Records",
        "Amory Music",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Evil Ink Records"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's second studio album, released in 2003?",
      choices: [
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "During the early years, what pseudonym did Claudio Sanchez use as the vocalist for Coheed and Cambria?",
      choices: [
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The Crowing",
        "The Prize Fighter Inferno",
        "The Running Free",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Prize Fighter Inferno"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the single 'The Running Free'?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2004, Coheed and Cambria joined the lineup of which major music festival, boosting their exposure?",
      choices: ["Coachella", "Lollapalooza", "Reading Festival", "Bonnaroo"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Lollapalooza"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's first music video, released in 2002?",
      choices: [
        "The Suffering",
        "A Favor House Atlantic",
        "Devil in Jersey City",
        "Blood Red Summer",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A Favor House Atlantic"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2004, Coheed and Cambria released a live DVD capturing a performance in New York. What is the title of this DVD?",
      choices: [
        "Live at the Roxy",
        "Neverender: Children of the Fence Edition",
        "The Last Supper: Live at Hammerstein Ballroom",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV Live",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Last Supper: Live at Hammerstein Ballroom"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's official podcast where the band discusses various topics?",
      choices: [
        "The Unheavenly Podcast",
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
        "The Coheed Cast",
        "Heed Your Call",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Coheed Cast"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2012, Coheed and Cambria released a double album. What are the titles of the two parts?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension and The Afterman: Descension",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: From Fear Through the Eyes of Madness and The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow and The Afterman: Descension",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3 and Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Ascension and The Afterman: Descension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the song 'A Favor House Atlantic,' which gained mainstream success?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2009, Coheed and Cambria embarked on a tour where they performed which two albums in their entirety?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension and The Afterman: Descension",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV and No World for Tomorrow",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3 and Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade and In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV and No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's fifth studio album, released in 2010?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "The Color Before the Sun",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2020, Coheed and Cambria released an album with a unique concept inspired by the Apollo space program. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "During the early years, Coheed and Cambria released music under the name Shabütie. What inspired the name change?",
      choices: [
        "A legal dispute",
        "A desire for a fresh start",
        "A suggestion from a fan",
        "A change in musical direction",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A legal dispute"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which song by Coheed and Cambria is known for its extended guitar solo and was released as a single in 2005?",
      choices: ["The Crowing", "Welcome Home", "The Suffering", "Feathers"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Suffering"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's drummer who joined the band in 2016?",
      choices: ["Chris Pennie", "Taylor Hawkins", "Nate Kelley", "Josh Eppard"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Josh Eppard"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2001, Coheed and Cambria released their second studio album. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is known for his distinctive voice and guitar work and is the primary songwriter for the band?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Josh Eppard",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's third studio album was released in 2005. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's first-ever headlining tour, launched in 2004?",
      choices: [
        "The Unheavenly Tour",
        "The Neverender Tour",
        "The Amory Wars Tour",
        "The Coheed Chronicles Tour",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Neverender Tour"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which famous record producer worked with Coheed and Cambria on their debut album 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "Rick Rubin",
        "Butch Vig",
        "David Bottrill",
        "Michael Birnbaum",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Michael Birnbaum"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's sixth studio album, released in 2012?",
      choices: [
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Ascension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is known for his work as a comic book artist and has created much of the band's album artwork?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2013, Coheed and Cambria released a concept album that served as a prequel to 'The Amory Wars' storyline. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Ascension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the graphic novel that Claudio Sanchez co-wrote, providing additional details about 'The Amory Wars' universe?",
      choices: [
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Afterman",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Bag.On.Line Adventures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's first-ever studio album, released in 2002?",
      choices: [
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria originally played bass guitar and later switched to lead guitar?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Josh Eppard",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2019, Coheed and Cambria went on tour with a band that shares its name with a famous amusement park. What is the name of this band?",
      choices: ["Disneyland", "Six Flags", "Universal Studios", "Cedar Point"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Mastodon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the acoustic album released by Coheed and Cambria in 2019?",
      choices: [
        "The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "The Color Before the Sun",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Color Before the Sun"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2007, Coheed and Cambria released a compilation album featuring early demos and unreleased tracks. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Penelope EP",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "The Lost Shepherd",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Lost Shepherd"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character who serves as the protagonist in 'The Amory Wars' narrative created by Claudio Sanchez?",
      choices: ["Coheed Kilgannon", "Sirius Amory", "The Crowing", "Ambellina"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Crowing"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2008, Coheed and Cambria released a studio album featuring a song inspired by the film 'The NeverEnding Story.' What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which record label signed Coheed and Cambria for their debut album 'The Second Stage Turbine Blade'?",
      choices: [
        "Columbia Records",
        "Equal Vision Records",
        "Roadrunner Records",
        "Atlantic Records",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Equal Vision Records"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2018, Coheed and Cambria collaborated with a popular rapper on the song 'The Dark Sentencer.' Who was the rapper?",
      choices: ["Eminem", "Travis Scott", "Kid Cudi", "Logic"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Scott"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's first live album, released in 2004?",
      choices: [
        "Live at the Apollo",
        "Live at the Roxy",
        "The Last Supper: Live at Hammerstein Ballroom",
        "Live at CBGB",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Live at the Roxy"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's second studio album, released in 2003?",
      choices: [
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's discography often references a science fiction narrative called 'The Amory Wars.' Who is the primary creator of this storyline?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2005, Coheed and Cambria contributed a cover of a popular song to a tribute album. What was the title of the song they covered?",
      choices: [
        "Bohemian Rhapsody",
        "Wish You Were Here",
        "Purple Haze",
        "Karma Police",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Wish You Were Here"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of Coheed and Cambria's official fan club, providing exclusive content and access to events?",
      choices: [
        "Children of the Fence",
        "Keywork Crew",
        "Amory Elite",
        "The Unheavenly Host",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Children of the Fence"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2017, Coheed and Cambria released a single that was also featured in the soundtrack of a popular animated film. What is the title of this single?",
      choices: [
        "Old Flames",
        "You Got Spirit, Kid",
        "Here to Mars",
        "The Afterman",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["You Got Spirit, Kid"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which Coheed and Cambria album features the character 'Ambellina,' a prominent figure in 'The Amory Wars' storyline?",
      choices: [
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's fourth studio album, released in 2007?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's album 'Year of the Black Rainbow' serves as a prequel to 'The Amory Wars' storyline. What character does it primarily focus on?",
      choices: ["Sirius Amory", "Ambellina", "Coheed Kilgannon", "The Writer"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sirius Amory"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2018, Coheed and Cambria embarked on a tour named after a significant element in 'The Amory Wars' universe. What was the title of this tour?",
      choices: [
        "The Keywork Chronicles Tour",
        "The Vaxis Voyage Tour",
        "The Amory Wars Tour",
        "The Unheavenly Creatures Tour",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Unheavenly Creatures Tour"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the graphic novel series co-written by Claudio Sanchez that expands on 'The Amory Wars' narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman",
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Keywork Chronicles"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2014, Coheed and Cambria released an album that marked a departure from 'The Amory Wars' concept. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "The Color Before the Sun",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Color Before the Sun"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the character Claudio Sanchez portrayed in the music video for the song 'A Favor House Atlantic'?",
      choices: [
        "Sirius Amory",
        "The Crowing",
        "Ambellina",
        "Claudio Kilgannon",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Kilgannon"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2006, Coheed and Cambria released an exclusive track for the soundtrack of a popular video game. Which game featured their song 'Welcome Home'?",
      choices: [
        "Guitar Hero III: Legends of Rock",
        "Fallout 3",
        "Halo 3",
        "Rock Band",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Guitar Hero III: Legends of Rock"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's song 'The Suffering' gained significant radio play. In which year was it released as a single?",
      choices: ["2003", "2005", "2007", "2009"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["2005"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which famous comic book artist collaborated with Claudio Sanchez on 'The Amory Wars' comic book series?",
      choices: ["Jim Lee", "Todd McFarlane", "Alex Ross", "Brian Bolland"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Jim Lee"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria released a live album in 2019, capturing performances from their 'Neverender' tour. What is the title of this live album?",
      choices: [
        "The Unheavenly Creatures Tour: Live",
        "Neverender: Children of the Fence Edition",
        "Live at the Apollo",
        "The Last Supper: Live at Hammerstein Ballroom",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Neverender: Children of the Fence Edition"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the song that served as the lead single for Coheed and Cambria's album 'Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures'?",
      choices: [
        "The Dark Sentencer",
        "The Gutter",
        "Old Flames",
        "Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Dark Sentencer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2011, Coheed and Cambria performed their album 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV' in its entirety. What was the special name given to this tour?",
      choices: [
        "The Good Apollo Tour",
        "The Ascension Tour",
        "The Burning Star Tour",
        "Neverender: SSTB",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Neverender: SSTB"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's fourth studio album, 'No World for Tomorrow,' was released in 2007. What is the title of the opening track on this album?",
      choices: [
        "Feathers",
        "The End Complete I: The Fall of House Atlantic",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "The Hound (Of Blood and Rank)",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The End Complete I: The Fall of House Atlantic"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2016, Coheed and Cambria released a compilation album featuring demos and rare tracks. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "The Lost Shepherd",
        "Rarities Vol. 1",
        "The Unraveling Palette of Dawn",
        "Past is Prologue",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Rarities Vol. 1"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2013, Coheed and Cambria released a double album as the ninth installment in 'The Amory Wars' series. What are the titles of the two parts of this album?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension and The Afterman: Descension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow and The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures and The Afterman: Descension",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3 and Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Ascension and The Afterman: Descension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is known for his side project 'The Prize Fighter Inferno'?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Josh Eppard",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria released an album in 2009 that serves as a prequel to 'The Amory Wars' saga. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Year of the Black Rainbow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2010, Coheed and Cambria performed a series of concerts called 'Neverender: SSTB.' What album did they play in its entirety during this tour?",
      choices: [
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria joined the band in 2007, filling the role of bassist?",
      choices: ["Zach Cooper", "Michael Todd", "Josh Eppard", "Travis Stever"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Michael Todd"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's fifth studio album, released in 2008?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["No World for Tomorrow"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2015, Coheed and Cambria went on tour with another prog-rock band, showcasing their affinity for complex musical compositions. What was the name of this tour?",
      choices: [
        "The Complexity Tour",
        "The Prog Odyssey Tour",
        "The Neverender Tour",
        "The Color Before the Sun Tour",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Color Before the Sun Tour"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the song that served as the lead single for Coheed and Cambria's album 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Vol. 2 – No World for Tomorrow'?",
      choices: [
        "The Running Free",
        "Feathers",
        "Mother Superior",
        "The End Complete III: The End Complete",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Running Free"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's song 'Welcome Home' gained popularity as the soundtrack for a trailer of a highly anticipated video game. Which game featured this trailer?",
      choices: ["Gears of War", "Halo 2", "Assassin's Creed", "Fallout 3"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Gears of War"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2017, Coheed and Cambria released an album that continued 'The Amory Wars' narrative. What is the title of this album?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "The Color Before the Sun",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's song 'Blood Red Summer' gained popularity and was featured on which of their albums?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2018, Coheed and Cambria released a coffee table book. What is the title of this book?",
      choices: [
        "The Amory Wars: Chronicles",
        "The Keywork Compendium",
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Coheed Chronicles",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Amory Wars: Chronicles"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the song that served as the lead single for Coheed and Cambria's album 'The Afterman: Descension'?",
      choices: [
        "Key Entity Extraction IV: Evagria the Faithful",
        "Gravity's Union",
        "Dark Side of Me",
        "The Hard Sell",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Key Entity Extraction IV: Evagria the Faithful"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2005, Coheed and Cambria released a limited edition version of their album 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV.' What was the special feature of this edition?",
      choices: [
        "Exclusive bonus track",
        "Graphic novel adaptation",
        "Signed poster",
        "3D album cover",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Graphic novel adaptation"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's album 'The Afterman: Descension' continues the story of a character introduced in 'The Afterman: Ascension.' What is the name of this character?",
      choices: ["Sirius Amory", "The Writer", "The Keywork", "Al the Killer"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Writer"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2017, Coheed and Cambria announced their collaboration with a brewery to release a signature beer. What is the name of this beer?",
      choices: [
        "Welcome Home Wheat",
        "Unheavenly Brew",
        "Gravity's Union IPA",
        "Keywork Lager",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Unheavenly Brew"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the documentary film released in 2009 that provides a behind-the-scenes look at Coheed and Cambria's tour life?",
      choices: [
        "The Fiction Will See the Real",
        "Neverender: Children of the Fence Edition",
        "On the Road with Coheed and Cambria",
        "Behind the Keywork",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Neverender: Children of the Fence Edition"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2016, Coheed and Cambria embarked on a tour to celebrate the 10th anniversary of a specific album. Which album was it?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is known for his distinctive guitar work and often collaborates with Claudio Sanchez in creating the band's sound?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Josh Eppard",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's album 'The Afterman: Ascension' features a song with a guest appearance by which famous musician?",
      choices: [
        "Serj Tankian",
        "Maynard James Keenan",
        "Chino Moreno",
        "Corey Taylor",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Serj Tankian"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2012, Coheed and Cambria released a double album as the eighth installment in 'The Amory Wars' series. What are the titles of the two parts of this album?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension and The Afterman: Descension",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow and The Afterman: Ascension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures and The Afterman: Descension",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3 and Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Afterman: Ascension and The Afterman: Descension"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is known for his distinctive drumming style and joined the band in 2007?",
      choices: [
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Travis Stever",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Josh Eppard",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Josh Eppard"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's album 'Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures' was released in 2018. What is the name of the character introduced in this album?",
      choices: ["Sirius Amory", "The Gutter", "Vic the Butcher", "Creature"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vic the Butcher"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2004, Coheed and Cambria released a live DVD featuring footage from a concert in New York City. What is the title of this live DVD?",
      choices: [
        "Live at the Roxy",
        "The Last Supper: Live at Hammerstein Ballroom",
        "Live at CBGB",
        "Neverender: Children of the Fence Edition",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Live at the Hammerstein Ballroom"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's song 'Ten Speed (Of God's Blood & Burial)' is part of which studio album?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the comic book series co-written by Claudio Sanchez that serves as a prequel to 'The Amory Wars' narrative?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman",
        "The Bag.On.Line Adventures",
        "The Keywork Chronicles",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Keywork Chronicles"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2013, Coheed and Cambria performed a concert where they played their album 'In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3' in its entirety. What was the name of this tour?",
      choices: [
        "The Neverender Tour",
        "The In Keeping Secrets Tour",
        "The Silent Earth Tour",
        "The Coheed Chronicles Tour",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Neverender Tour"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the song that served as the lead single for Coheed and Cambria's album 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Vol. 1 – From Fear Through The Eyes of Madness'?",
      choices: [
        "Welcome Home",
        "The Suffering",
        "The Willing Well IV: The Final Cut",
        "Apollo I: The Writing Writer",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Suffering"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's album 'No World for Tomorrow' features a song with a guest appearance by which famous musician?",
      choices: [
        "Maynard James Keenan",
        "Serj Tankian",
        "Chino Moreno",
        "Corey Taylor",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Maynard James Keenan"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2015, Coheed and Cambria released an animated video for the song 'You Got Spirit, Kid.' Who directed this animated video?",
      choices: [
        "Wes Anderson",
        "Robert Rodriguez",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Jon Schnepp",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Claudio Sanchez"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's song 'Feathers' is featured on which studio album?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2011, Coheed and Cambria collaborated with another artist to release a split single. Who was the collaborating artist?",
      choices: [
        "Between the Buried and Me",
        "Circa Survive",
        "The Dear Hunter",
        "The Used",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Between the Buried and Me"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of Coheed and Cambria's first studio album, released in 2002?",
      choices: [
        "Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV",
        "In Keeping Secrets of Silent Earth: 3",
        "The Second Stage Turbine Blade",
        "No World for Tomorrow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Second Stage Turbine Blade"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2014, Coheed and Cambria released a song that was used as the end credits theme for a popular animated TV series. What is the title of this song?",
      choices: ["Here to Mars", "Island", "Colors", "The Hard Sell"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Island"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's album 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Vol. 2 – No World for Tomorrow' features a song with a guest appearance by which famous musician?",
      choices: [
        "Serj Tankian",
        "Maynard James Keenan",
        "Chino Moreno",
        "Corey Taylor",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Chino Moreno"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2016, Coheed and Cambria released a song as a tribute to a legendary artist who passed away that year. Who was the artist they paid tribute to?",
      choices: ["David Bowie", "Prince", "Leonard Cohen", "George Michael"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["David Bowie"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the title of the Coheed and Cambria documentary that provides an in-depth look at the making of their album 'Good Apollo, I'm Burning Star IV: Vol. 1 – From Fear Through The Eyes of Madness'?",
      choices: [
        "Behind the Keywork",
        "The Fiction Will See the Real",
        "Neverender: Children of the Fence Edition",
        "From Fear to Eternity",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["The Fiction Will See the Real"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's song 'The Dark Sentencer' serves as the opening track for which album?",
      choices: [
        "The Afterman: Ascension",
        "The Afterman: Descension",
        "Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures",
        "Year of the Black Rainbow",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Vaxis - Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 2003, Coheed and Cambria released a single that gained mainstream success and was featured in the soundtrack of a popular video game. What is the title of this single?",
      choices: [
        "Welcome Home",
        "A Favor House Atlantic",
        "Blood Red Summer",
        "The Suffering",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["A Favor House Atlantic"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria's album 'The Color Before the Sun' marks a departure from their concept albums. What inspired Claudio Sanchez to write this album?",
      choices: [
        "Personal experiences and emotions",
        "Science fiction literature",
        "Classic mythology",
        "The works of Edgar Allan Poe",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Personal experiences and emotions"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member of Coheed and Cambria is known for his skills as a multi-instrumentalist and has contributed to the band's diverse sound?",
      choices: [
        "Travis Stever",
        "Claudio Sanchez",
        "Zach Cooper",
        "Josh Eppard",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Travis Stever"],
      score: 5,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Coheed and Cambria performed a cover of a famous track for a tribute album dedicated to the original artist. Which song did they cover, and who was the original artist?",
      choices: [
        "Comfortably Numb by Pink Floyd",
        "Dream On by Aerosmith",
        "Bohemian Rhapsody by Queen",
        "Hotel California by Eagles",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Bohemian Rhapsody by Queen"],
      score: 5,
    },
  ],
};
